tv-radio.com 2018-12-16

# Privacy Policy Information | Arkena

This website [http://www.arkena.com](http://www.arkena.com/) is Arkena’s wesbite.

Arkena’s head office is based at 15, rue Cognacq-Jay 75007 Paris, France.

### **What personal data we collect and why we collect it**

#### **Contact forms**

When you fill a contact form, you inform us about your first name, last name, country, company, job title, number and e-mail address. Thanks to these informations, we can contact you back and understand your needs.

**Download forms**

If you download a document on our website (use cases, product sheets…), you have to fill a form with your last name, first name, e-mail address, country, company and job title. These are for the optimization of the user experience and in the interest for Arkena to adapt communication to every user’s unique interests.

**Cookies**

This website uses cookies.

Some cookies on this site are essential, and the site won’t work as expected without them. These cookies are set when you submit a form, login or interact with the site by doing something that goes beyond clicking on simple links.

We also use some non-essential cookies to anonymously track visitors or enhance your experience of the site. If you’re not happy with this, we won’t set these cookies but some nice features of the site may be unavailable.

If you do not accept cookies, you can block them in your browser security settings. You can also ask your browser to warn you every time a website attempts to place a cookie on your computer.

Cookies are small text files stored on your computer. Cookies are commonly used to improve the site for the user, for example, to adapt a website to the visitor’s preferences, choices and interests.

No personal information, such as the visitors e-mail or name, is automatically saved.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

#### **Embedded content from other websites**

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

#### **Who we share your data with?**

We do not share your data with a third party.

#### **What rights you have over your data?**

  * If you have filed a form on this website, you can ask for an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us.

  * You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you by sending a mail to [hello@arkena.com](mailto:hello@arkena.com). This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

#### **Where we send your data**

Data are sent to our Marketing automation solution.

### Security

Our marketing automation solution provides us secure solution in accordance with their [Trust and Compliance documentation](https://help.salesforce.com/articleView?id=Pardot-Trust-and-Compliance-Documentation&type=1).

If you have questions regarding our privacy practices, please mail us at:  [hello@arkena.com .](mailto:hello@arkena.com)
